声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
在这儿了 这就是我们的当务之急
Right now, this is our priority.
Danielle 你是怎么来这个岛的?
How did you come to be on this island, Danielle?
船撞在了岩石上 搁浅了
The ship slammed into rocks,ran aground.
等一下 伙计 你现在要什么?
Hold on a second, dude.You want what now?
你想做雪球?
You wanna make snowballs?
他要你抱紧那些竹子
Hold the bamboo tighter.
我认为是这样的
I think.
干得怎样了?
How's it coming?
不错
It's coming.
只要没有人搞破坏就行了 是吗?
Long as nobody sabotages this one as well, huh?
我让人24小时守着了
I got people standing guard 24/7.
任何企图想破环的或没这企图的人都进不来
Nobody gets near this,with or without intent to burn.
听着 我一直在想
I was thinking, uh,the chances of a passing ship
过往的船只看到这只救生艇的机会很小
spotting this raft out there is pretty slim.
我们能用点什么
We could use something to send a distress call
给可能在这附近的船只送去遇险信号
to any ship that might be close.
就像S.O.S.
Like an SOS.
好的 听着 我会去找Sayid的
OK. I'll ask Sayid,
但是就算他能做出一些那样的东西
but even if he could make something like that,
他也没有能源能使它运行
he's not gonna have anything to power it with.
Sayid没说过那个疯狂的法国女人有电池吗?
Didn't Sayid say that crazy French chick had batteries?
绝对没有
Absolutely not.
-我没有叫你去  -我会去的
-I'm not asking you to go.  -I'll do it.
伙计 我们只是...
We're trying...
你们真的以为她会放弃一些生存的必需品吗
Do you think she would give up something
而且是给一个完全的陌生人?
she needs to a stranger?
我所问的只是让你告诉我怎么找到她 只有这些
All I'm asking is for you to tell me how to find her. That's it.
我被带去她的营地时已经是人事不省了
I was brought unconscious to her camp.
当我逃出时 我更象是一只无头苍蝇  我不知道怎么找到她
I was disoriented. I don't know how to find her.
不知道 伙计 还是不想说?
Don't know, dude? Or don't want to?
Sayid 听着 你有她的地图和一些纸张
Sayid, look. You've got her maps and her papers.
并且你认为它们能代表什么
You thought they were pointing to something.
可能那些纸张和地图可以让我们找到她呢
Maybe they're pointing to her.
听着 我甚至不知这些纸张说明了什么
Look! I don't know what these papers mean!
我只知道 它们可能是她脑子不清时的胡言乱语
They could be the ravings of her disturbed mind.
夹杂着方程式的歌词
Song lyrics, mixed with equations!
如果这张地图能找到她
If this map is pointing to her,
那么你得知道她住在这里 在这块区域
then you should know she resides here in this area.
她给那地方取名为 Territoire Fonce
She gave it a name."Territoire Fonce. "
Shannon翻译后说它意思是黑暗的领土
Shannon translated it.It means "Dark Territory."
那听起来像是一个你想去的地方吗?
That sound like a place you'd like to visit?
这么说你不帮忙了?
So you won't help?
我没这么说
I didn't say that.
我会造一座代表我们遇险的灯塔
I'll build the distress beacon.
但是我建议你去找另外的能源
I suggest you find another power source.
驾驶员舱里肯定会有些什么
Something in the cockpit.
我们不去驾驶员舱
We're not going to the cockpit.
Hugo你在那儿做什么?
What are you doing in there?
没什么 妈妈 只是看点东西
Uno momento, mama.I'm just checking something out.
我希望你别再看那些不良节目了
I hope you're not watching those G-string mujeres again.
听着 妈 我们来谈谈这个
Look, Ma, we talked about this.
你想让我住在这儿 你就得尊重我的隐私
If you want me living here,you gotta respect my privacy.
况且 我没在看
And no, I'm not.
看看你
Look at you.
周六晚上
It's Saturday night.
一个成年人坐在家里看电视
A grown-up man sitting at home watching TV.
你应该出去 试着帮你自己找个好女人
You should go out.Try to find yourself a nice woman.
好的 我会去的
I'll get right on that.
至少试着吃得好一点 你又胖了
Try eating better.You're gaining weight again.
大的号码是 42
with the Mega Number 42.
那就产生了今晚百万彩票的大奖
And that makes tonight's Mega Lotto Jackpot Drawing
4 8 15
16 和 23 加上一个大号码42
16 and 23 with the Mega Number 42.
谁有了这个号码就是赢家
Whoever has those numbers has won
否则奖金就会累积到下次中奖
or will share in a near record jackpot.
是的 Mary Jo 因为已经16周没有人得奖了
That's right, Mary Jo,because this is the sixteenth week without a winner.
你醒了?
You awake?
我只是对自己感到惊讶
I was just wondering that myself.
那么 那个法国女士 她写了这些 对么?
That French lady wrote this stuff?
Hurley 半夜三更的 你想干什么?
It's the middle of the night.What do you want?
睡不着
Couldn't sleep.
我很好奇
And I got curious.
你和Shannon...
You and Shannon,
你们一直试着指出这些东西 并且
you guys have been trying to figure out some of this stuff,
我想知道... 你知道
and I was wondering what...
你们指出了...
you guys figured out
这些东西
about this stuff?
-哪些东西?  -我不知道
-What stuff?  -I don't know.
看看这些她花了点时间写下的数字
Well, take these numbers she wrote down a bunch of times.
知道它说明什么么?
Got any idea what it means?
我认为在某时他们可能等价于什么
I thought at one time they might be coordinates of some kind.
等价 是的
Coordinates, yeah.
你第一次找到她...
But when you first found her,
那法国女人...
the French chick,
你说你在沙滩上看见了一条金属线或是什么
you said you saw a wire or something on the beach.
然后你沿着它 找到了她
You followed it, and it led you to her.
不是 它引我走进了一个她设的陷阱
No. It led me into a trap she set.
但是她的地方也不远了 是么?
But her place is probably close, right?
为什么你突然对Rousseau这么感兴趣?
Why are you interested in Rousseau?
我没有
I'm not.
只是 你知道 谈谈话 伙计
Just making conversation, dude.
对不起 如果这不是时候
Sorry if it's a bad time.
晚安
Good night.
是的 是的 你
Yeah, you.
你是怎么想到大奖号码的? 有什么意义么?
How did you come up with the winning numbers?
它们只是  突然想到的
they just, sorta came to me.
说说你的家庭吧?
Why don't you introduce your family?
好的
yeah, okay
这位...这位 害羞的美女是我妈妈Carmen 过来 妈
This bashful beauty is my mom, Carmen.Come here, Ma.
然后这是我的兄弟Diego和他的妻子Lisa
And this is my brother, Diego,and his wife, Lisa.
我们富有了!
We're rich!
好的 伙计 别理他 他是个傻蛋
Nice, dude.Ignore him.He's an idiot.
然后
And,
你们得见见这家伙
You gotta meet this guy.
这是我认识的最伟大的家伙 我的爷爷Tito
This is the greatest guy I know.My grandpa, Tito.
他有三个工作...到现在多久了?
He's worked three jobs for... How long's it been, Abuelito?
-52年  -52年
-52 years.  -52 years.
他70岁了
He's 70 years old,
他最近的一次度假
and the closest thing that he's had to a vacation
是在4年前得了一个标兵的称号
is when they put a pacemaker in him four years ago.
所以我拿这些钱来做的第一件事
The first thing I'll do
就是给他他以后所赚的全部的钱
with the money is to give him the rest he's earned.
因为对我来说十分重要的
That's what it's all about for me,
就是为我关心的人做些什么
to be able to do things for the people I care about.
因为最近我欠我的家庭很多
'Cause I really put my family through a lot recently,
所以  这样我就能弥补了
and, well, this way I can make it up to them.
你知道 可能给我妈妈买一幢新房子
You know, maybe even buy my mom a new house.
然后 在我爷爷航行回来时
And, Maybe after,my grandpa comes back from his cruise,
我们能 你们知道
we can get to do some of the things
做一些我们经常想要做的事
that we always wanted to do.
爷爷?
Grandpa?
什么 我什么都没做
What? I'm not doing anything.
什么
What?
什么?
我只是说早上好
Just saying good morning.
好的
Right.
早上好
Morning.
抱歉 我只是...
Sorry.I was just...
-去哪儿?  -我? 不
-You going somewhere?  -Me? No.
是的
Well, yeah
只是觉得我可以去散散步 呃
just thought I might take a walk.
可能找到一些 呃 新的垂钓地点
maybe scope out some, uh, new fishing area.
好了 我也去
I'll come with.
好的
That's okay.
不 我可以领略一下外面的新鲜空气
I could use a bit of the wide open.
伙计 我现在能一个人静静么
Dude, I could really use some alone time right now.
当然
Sure.
我人太大 很容易脱水
I'm a big guy.I get dehydrated easy.
是的
Yeah.
是的 好
Yeah, okay.
Claire
有空么?
you got a second?
是的 当然
sure.
我想你有空在工程上帮我一个忙么
I was wondering if you're free to help me with a little project.
-我?  -是的
-Me?  -Yeah.
我在造东西 我需要你的帮忙
I'm building something and I could use an extra pair of hands.
我怀孕快9个月了
I'm nine months pregnant.
我只能在沙滩上摇摇晃晃地走
I can barely waddle to the beach.
你能看一下么?
Could you hold a saw?
好的
yeah.
你的手能这样来来回回动么?
Can you move your hand back and forth?
可能吧
Possibly.
你真棒
You're perfect.
好的
Okay.
那么 我们在造什么?
So, what exactly are we building?
在哪儿?
Where is it?
什么在哪儿?
Where's what?
地图 我告诉过你它对你找到她没有作用
The map. It won't help you find her.
那张地图不在我这儿
I don't have it.
更坏的是这卑鄙勾当不是你自己干的
What's worse is you won't do your own dirty work.
-你让Hurley帮你做  -等等
-You get Hurley to do it.  -Wait a minute.
Hurley?
他昨晚在我的帐篷里向我盘问关于Rousseau的事情
He was in my tent last night.Quizzing me about Rousseau.
关于她写的数字
About numbers she wrote,
我怎么去找她
how I came to find her.
你什么都不知到 是不是?
You don't know anything about this, do you?
Charlie.
你看到Hurley了么?
have you seen Hurley?
几个小时前 他散步去了
Couple of hours ago.He was setting out for a walk.
像个笨蛋一样 我得说明
Acting like a loon, I might add.
天那 他去追踪她了
My God. He's going after her.
你什么时候回来?
When are you gonna be back?
我们能赶上他的话 天黑之前
If we catch him, before nightfall.
你担心我?
Are you worried about me?
如果我是呢?
So what if I am?
Sayid!
准备好了么?
You ready?
我会没事的
I'll be fine.
Hugo 把那噪音关掉
Hugo, turn that noise down.
抱歉
sorry.
带我去哪儿?
Where are you taking me?
你知道我不喜欢惊喜
You know I don't like surprises.
你会喜欢这样的 妈
You're gonna like this one, Ma.
我是说 当你经历了所有事情之后
I mean, after everything you've been through...
就像爷爷
like Grandpa
然后是葬礼
Then at the funeral,
神父Aguilar因为闪电而罢工
Father Aguilar getting struck by lightning.
那真荒谬
Man, that was a freak storm.
Diego在Lisa离开他跟着那个招待跑了之后搬会了家
And Diego moving back home after Lisa left him for that waitress.
别跟我提那个婊子
Don't mention that whore.
我只是说该是你享福的时候了
I'm just saying, you deserve something good to happen.
你知道...
You know,
从我中了彩票大奖之后 就像...
ever since I won the lottery, it's like...
我们除了坏运气还是坏运气
we've had nothing but bad luck.
就像... 我不知道
Like, I don't know,
钱的诅咒还是什么
the money's cursed or something.
胡说八道
That's blasphemy.
你知道我们是天主教徒 我们不相信诅咒
You know we are Catholic.We don't believe in curses.
妈 我只是说说
Jeez, Ma, I'm just talking.
好了 我们快到了 来 穿上这个
Okay, we're almost there.Here, put this on.
我为什么得穿这个?
Why do I have to wear this?
手 小心
Give me your hand. Careful.
不不 你...你小心
You be careful.
-下台阶  -我什么都看不见
-Stepping down.  -I can't see anything.
好的 现在拿下你的眼罩
Okay, now,take off your blindfold,
然后看看你的新的梦幻豪宅
and get a look at your new dream house.
我的脚踝  我的脚踝
My ankle.My ankle.
我说过你可以拿下你的眼罩了
I said take off your blindfold.
你起先为什么要我带上呢?
Why did you make me put that thing on?
Hugo 是有烟味么?
do I smell smoke?
混蛋
crap!
等下 妈 我打911
Hang on.ma. I gotta call 911.
好的 告诉他们我扭伤了我的脚踝
You tell them I broke my ankle.
放下电话 远离车子
Drop the phone.Move away from the vehicle.
不 不 不 是这房子 这是一个误会
No, no! It's the house.This is a mistake.
快 转过去
Do it! Now!Turn around.
没有诅咒这一说 是么 妈?
No such thing as curses, Ma?
你有权力保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
但是你所说的一切
Anything you say can and will
将成为呈堂证供
be used against you.
法国女人!
French chick!
我认为你会高兴的
I would think you'd be happy.
你的股票都涨了
Every one of your stocks is up.
你对这些厉害的暴风席卷佛罗里达后
Your interests in orange futures skyrocketed
留下的桔色的流星焰火感兴趣
after those tropical storms hit Florida.
并且你现在是Tustin一家制盒公司的股东
And you are now the majority shareholder for a box company in Tustin.
一家制盒公司?
A box company?
他们生产盒子
They make boxes.
有利的事业 每个人都需要盒子
Lucrative business.Everybody needs boxes.
这让我想到了...
Which reminds me,
你在加拿大的运动鞋厂...
your sneaker factory in Canada...
我在加拿大有鞋厂?
I own a sneaker factory in Canada?
不再有了
Well, not anymore.
上月在一场火中毁了
It was destroyed in a fire last month.
当然是这样了
Of course it was.
你可以认为是胡说八道 死了八个人
You might have read about it.Eight-something people died.
但是好消息是我们给这件事做了过保
But the good news is,we over-insured it.
这将使你发一笔横财
It's gonna yield you a windfall.
我们把它添加到从LAPD得来的有关你被非法拘留
And when we add in the generous settlement from the LAPD
的解决方案
for your false arrest,
你的资本净值在几个月内就会是现在的两倍
you've almost doubled your net worth in a few short months.
我还是无法想象警察怎么会把你当毒贩给逮捕起来的
I still can't imagine how the police mistook you for a drug dealer.
厄运
Bad luck.
Hugo 不只一个中彩票大奖的人
Hugo.You are not the first lottery winner to believe
会认为钱给他们带来的只是厄运
the money's brought nothing but trouble.
这些只是你脑子里想想的
It's all in your head.
什么 你不相信不详物这一说?
What, you don't believe in jinxes?
就像 诅咒?
You know, curses?
我是一个会计 我相信数字
I'm an accountant. I believe in numbers.
你从哪儿得到他们的?
where'd you get them, anyway?
什么?
What?
大奖号码 你用了...
The winning numbers. What'd you use...
某人的生日? 电话号码
Somebody's birthday? Phone number.
不是 这只是一些...
Nah, it's nothing. It's just something that I
-什么?  -就是了
-What?  -That's it.
这不是钱的问题 是号码的问题
It's not the money. It's the numbers.
这是被诅咒的号码
The numbers are cursed.
伙计 别这么看着我 我没疯 这真的是...
Dude, don't look at me like that. I'm not crazy. This is really
好了 Hugo 听你自己的 "钱是被诅咒的"
Come on, Hugo, listen to yourself. "The numbers are cursed."
你知道不会发生这些事 就像是...
You know there is no such thing as a
你要撞得更狠一些么?
You want to hit that a little harder?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我在做救我们命的逃生艇打扰了你么?
Is my building a raft to get us rescued bothering you?
就现在来说 是的
At the moment, yeah.
你为什么不来帮忙?
Why aren't you helping?
我正在帮忙...防着纵火犯
I am helping, short round...keeping watch for arsonists.
Walt说对了
Walt's got a point.
你可以更努力点
You could pitch in,
好像你已经买了逃生票一样
seeing as how you've already bought your ticket.
你是照我说的那样绑得么?
Did you tie this like I told you?
因为如果你是像我说的那样绑好了的话  那些东西就不会散了
'Cause if you'd have tied it like I said, the thing would still be together!
你怎么了? 你在想什么?
What's the matter with you? What is your problem?
他不会再和我说话了
He's never going to speak to me again.
他需要的是时间
He just needs time.
我让他丢脸了
I humiliated him.
当救生艇起航时...
When the raft sails...
你认为他会和他们一起走么?
do you think he's going to leave with them?
我不知道
I don't know.
别动
Don't move!
-你们这些家伙...  -Hurley 别动
-what are you guys  -Hurley, do not move.
你正站在一个压力触发机上
You're standing on a pressure trigger.
如果你走开 那个就会发射出来
If you take your weight off it, it will release that.
天那
man.
我们得找一些东西替代他的体重
We need to find something to replace his weight on the trigger.
代替他的体重? 我们能做到么?
Replace his weight? How are we going to do that?
别动
Don't move!
大家冷静一下
Everybody, just calm down.
我能放下这根线么?
Can I drop the wire?
-也许我能找到块岩石  -是的 大一点的
-Maybe I can find a rock.  -Yes, a big one.
-我要把线放了  -Hurley 不
-I'm dropping the wire.  -Hurley, no!
我能做到
I can make it.
Hurley 别动
Hurley, don't move!
我能逃掉的 我很敏捷
I can get out of the way. I'm spry.
Hurley 原位别动
Hurley, stay put!
Hurley Hurley 别...
Hurley! Hurley! Don't even
Hurley 你到底是怎么了?
Hurley, what the bloody hell is wrong with you?!
没什么
Nothing.
你在这儿干什么 伙计?
What are you doing out here, man?
我来拿电池
I came to get a battery.
Hurley 认真点
Hurley, seriously.
怎么了?
What's going on?
你们也来么?
You guys coming?
你们都想去?
You all want to go?
好的
Fine.
但是要我来打头
But perhaps I should take the lead.
好想法
Excellent notion.
Lenny 他叫Lenny 或是 Leonard.
Lenny. His name is Lenny. Or Leonard.
但是你不知他姓什么
But you don't know his last name.
听着 我只想和他说5分钟的话
Look, I just need to talk to him for five minutes.
抱歉 但是先生  如果你不能说出病人的名字
I'm sorry, but if you can't tell me the patient's name, sir,
我就不能查了
I can't very well look it up.
这儿有多少Leonards?
How many Leonards are here?
只是...你不能只是打入"Leonard"?
Just...can't you just type in "Leonard"?
我是说 这家伙就像永远呆在这儿了 他认识我
I mean, the guy's been here for, like, ever. He knows me.
我们的纪录是保密的 先生 任何人...
Our records are private, sir, and anybody...
伙计 现在别干那个
Dude, do not do that right now!
下次再来修 你这家伙
Leave the bulb for another time, man.
5分钟
Five minutes.
我只要5分钟
All I need is five minutes.
Hugo?
医生
doc.
见到你真好 你回来干什么?
It's good to see you. What are you doing back here?
我不记得你和Leonard这么亲密 Hugo.
I don't remember you and Leonard being that close, Hugo.
是的 我们来
Yeah, well, we hung.
我会留给你们的 要么
I'll leave you gentlemen to it, then.
好运 Hugo
Good luck, Hugo.
Lenny.
记得我么?
Remember me?
Hugo
Hurley
我...
Well, I was...
我只是 你知道 在附近 而且
I was just, you know,in the neighborhood, and,
听着 Lenny 我要知道...
Look, Lenny, I got to know
那些号码代表着什么?
what do the numbers mean?
4 8 15 16 23 42  4 8 15 16 23 42...
它们对你有害么?
Did they do something to you?
因为我觉得他们对我有害
'Cause I think they did something to me.
我认为他们使我变成了一个倒霉蛋
I think they turned me into a jinx.
对我周围的人而言的扫把星
Bad news to everyone around me.
当我和大家说 我觉得我是起因时 他们...
And when I tell people, I think I'm the cause, they
他们..他们看着我就像在看白痴
they...they look at me like I'm nuts.
他们不相信我
They don't believe me.
但是我知道
But I know.
自从我用这些号码赢了彩票后
Ever since I won the lottery with those numbers.
你用这些号码去买彩票了?
You used those numbers to play the lottery?
是的
yeah.
你不该这么做的
You shouldn't have done that.
你把盒子打开了
You've opened the box!
你不应该用这些号码的
You shouldn't have used the numbers!
它还没停下 你得远离那些号码
It doesn't stop! You got to get away from those numbers!
你得离的远远的 越远越好
You got to get far, far away!
你听见我说的么
Do you hear me?!
你难道不知道
Don't you understand?!
你得远离它 否则它不会停下的
You got to get away from them or it won't stop!
等一下 等一下 我需要答案
Wait a sec, wait a sec. I need some answers.
先生 你得离远点
Sir, you need to step away.
Lenny 这些号码 你从哪儿来的?
Lenny, the numbers! Where'd you get them?
Sam Toomey 他听来的
Sam Toomey! He heard them!
谁是Sam Toomey?
Who's Sam Toomey?
他从Kalgoorlie听来的
He heard them in Kalgoorlie.
什么是Kalgoorlie?
What's Kalgoorlie?
那是一个我们曾经工作过的镇
It's a town where we used to work.
哪儿的镇?
A town where?
在澳大利亚
In Australia!
天那
Oh, god!
在这儿没了了 伸入地下了
It stops here. It goes into the ground.
这有点困难
This poses somewhat of a problem.
伙计们
Guys,
你们来看看这个
you should come see this.
你从没提到过桥
You never mentioned anything about a bridge.
我从没看见过
I never saw this before.
她不可能凭一己之力造出这座桥的
There's no way she could have built this all by herself.
是的 但是她的队伍可以
No, but her team could have.
或是Ethan的队伍
Or Ethan's team.
Hurley 你在做什么?
Hurley, what are you doing?
放松点 我只是去看看
Relax. I'm just going to check it out.
你们得呆在这儿
You guys should stay here.
Hurley 快回来
Hurley, get back here!
伙计 别扫兴
Dudes, chill.
Charlie
他都能过去...
if he can do it...
Charlie 快
Charlie! Move!
伙计 还好吧
Dude, you okay?
我很好
I'm okay!
好的 你们在那儿别动
All right, you two stay put right there.
我们再去找条路
We're going to find a way around,
然后我们去那儿找你们
and we'll meet you there.
那 反过来 你们呆那儿
Nah, screw that. You guys stay.
这儿有条小路 Charlie...
There's a path right here. Charlie...
Hurley 闭嘴听Jack的吧 他叫我们别动
Hurley, will you shut up and listen to Jack?! He said stay put!
你就像一个嗜血的疯子
You're acting like a bloody lunatic!
如果这不是一个荒野之地  我会说你迷路了
If this weren't the middle of nowhere, I'd say you were lost.
这是Sam Toomey的家么?
Is this Sam Toomey's house?
是的 我是他妻子
It is. I'm his wife.
他在么?
Well, is he around?
我想找他说些话
'Cause I'd kind of like to talk to him.
我也想和他说话 但是Sam已经死了4年了
I'd like that, too, but Sam's been dead for four years.
你的丈夫和我认识的一个人工作过...Leonard Simms
Your husband worked with a guy I know...Leonard Simms.
是的 他们同在美国海军服役
That's right. They served together in the U.S. Navy.
Leonard怎样了? 还在当兵?
How is Leonard? Still in the service?
他...
he's...
退役了
retired.
不管怎样... 他和我说了Sam...
Anyway... he told me about Sam...
听到了些什么
hearing something.
你在说号码是么
You're talking about the numbers.
是的 就是那些号码
Yes. The numbers. Exactly.
你知道一些什么么?
Do you know anything about them?
Sam和Leonard在一个潜听哨站岗
Sam and Leonard were stationed at a listening post
监视横跨太平洋的电波
monitoring longwave transmissions over the pacific.
无聊的工作 Sam很讨厌
Boring job. Sam hated it.
没事可做 只是一夜又一夜地听着静电噪声
Nothing to do but listen to static night after night
直到16年前的一个晚上
till one night, back 16 years ago,
电波里有些东西
there's something in the static.
有一个声音
A voice cuts through
有一个声音不断的重复那些号码  一遍又一遍
a voice repeating those numbers over and over again.
几天后 天晴了 我们在Kalgoorlie
Couple of days later, we're at the fair in Kalgoorlie,
有这么一个罐子
and some wally there's got this jar.
像小马一样大
Must have been big as a pony,
边上镶满了豆子
and it's filled to the rim with beans.
小姑娘给任何一个在10次内可以猜对罐子里豆子数的人
Filly's offering 50 grand to anyone able to guess
罐子里豆子数的人
how many beans are in that jar
5万美元
within 10.
Sam用了那些数字
Sam used the numbers.
是的
Yep.
答案和豆子数刚好吻合
The answer was exact to the bean.
人们已经做这个游戏40年了
Man had been running the same scam for 40 years.
没有人说过接近的数字
Nobody'd ever come close.
所以我们赢了钱了
So we won the money.
回家路上
On the way home,
一辆卡车在高速公路上撞到了一棵树
a pickup truck blows a tire on the highway,
迎面撞伤了我们
hits us head-on.
那夜我失去了一只脚
Lost my leg that night.
Sam怎样?
What about Sam?
仅仅擦破了点皮
Barely a scratch.
大部分人会认为他很幸运
Most people would consider themselves lucky,
但是他没有
but not him.
从那以后他变了
He was never the same after that.
他开始写纪录
He started keeping a record.
纪录一切周围的人
发生的可怕的事...
Anything terrible that happened to anyone around us
他认为这全怪他用了那些数字
he believed it was all because he used those numbers.
他把我们搬到了这个荒野之地  希望能停止厄运
He moved us out here in the middle of nowhere, hoping it would stop.
成功了么?
Did it?
他找到能让厄运停止的办法了么?
Did he ever find a way to make it stop?
他拿着一把短枪放入他的嘴里扣动了扳机
He put a shotgun in his mouth and pulled the trigger.
你怎么了 Reyes先生?
What is it you're looking for, mr. Reyes?
我用它们...
I used them
那些数字
the numbers
赢了彩票
to win the lottery.
现在我认为我受到了相同的诅咒
And now I think I'm under the same curse.
诅咒?
Curse?
没有什么诅咒
There's no curse.
但你刚刚和我说...
But you just told me
你认为我的脚还在
You think I'd still have my leg
如果Sam没有说对豆子的确切数目的话?
if Sam hadn't have picked the right number of beans?
你认为那个洪水就不会爆发了?
You think that floods wouldn't have happened,
那个...那个房子就不会被烧毁
that...that homes wouldn't have burned down,
那些人就不会死?
that people wouldn't have died?
是的
Well, yeah.
你的命运如此 Reyes先生
You make your own luck, mr. Reyes.
别怪到这些混蛋的号码身上
Don't blame it on the damn numbers.
你只是在找一个并不存在的借口
You're looking for an excuse that doesn't exist.
这是个陷阱 是么?
It's a trap, right?
为了抓动物?
For catching animals?
拜托给我那个杯子?
Pass me that cup, please?
这黏黏的是什么?
what's this gunk?
胶水
Glue.
你在哪儿找到胶水的?
Where'd you find glue?
我从动物的脂肪里提炼出来的
I made it out of rendered animal fat.
你会做胶水?
You made glue?
你应该开一个秀场
You should have one of those shows where you,
就在你为人们造房子的地方
fix up houses for people.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
谢谢
Thanks.
为了你...给了我一些做的事情
For this --giving me something to do.
我 我已经厌倦了想着在那儿发生的我的那些事
I'm , tired of trying to remember what happened to me out there.
那些是怎么来的?
How's that coming?
你的回忆?
Your memory?
这儿的那儿的一些零零碎碎地小事
Bits and pieces here and there.
没什么是真正有意义的
Nothing that makes any real sense.
也许我能帮忙
Well, maybe I can help.
我对于将零碎的小东西凑起来很在行
I'm good at putting bits and pieces together.
怎么了?
What?
这儿很眼熟 这块地方
This is familiar...this area.
我们接近了
We're close.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
我认为她住在地下
I thought she lived underground.
Jack
那该死的是什么?
What the hell was that?
该死的防卫系统
Hell of a security system.
某人绊到了线 这些地方全炸开了
Somebody trips a wire, and the whole place blows up.
这儿没东西
There's nothing here.
-电池?  -没什么
-The batteries?  -Nothing.
我不懂
I don't get it.
她知道了
She knew.
她知道某天我会回来并且带着别人
She knew that one day I'd come back and bring others.
所以她放弃了这个地方
So she abandoned this place,
在这儿设了陷阱
booby-trapped it,
然后搬走了
and moved on.
搬去哪儿?
Moved on where?
Jack
Sayid
我们知道我们是去那儿么?
Do we even know where we're going?
爆炸的冲击波好像是从这边来的  我认为是
The blast sounded like it came from this way, I think.
但是你不知道
But you don't know.
伙计 你想从我这儿得到什么
Dude, what do you want from me?
我想要什么?
What do I want?
我想知道我们来这种荒野之地做什么
I wanna know what we're doing in the middle of nowhere.
别和我说是为了那些该死的电池
And don't tell me it's because of some stinking batteries.
一会儿你是个快乐开心好运的Hurley
One minute you're happy-go-luckygood-time Hurley
一会儿你又成了血腥讨厌呆板的Kurtz
and the next you're colonel bloody Kurtz.
这毫无道理 这不是你
It just doesn't make any sense. It's not you.
伙计 你不了解我
Dude, you don't know me.
在岛上的这么多时候  你从没和我说起过你自己
Well, all this time on the island, you've told me nothing about yourself.
我们都有隐私 伙计
We all got personal stuff, dude.
别转移话题
Don't change the subject.
我们在这儿迷路了
We're lost out here.
Jack和Sayid如果没被炸成碎片的话那肯定是受伤了
Jack and Sayid could be hurt, if not blown to bits,
全都怪你扮得像个血腥的疯子
all because you're acting like some bloody nutter.
我没疯
I am not crazy.
-我是有原因的 为了...  -我认为我有权利知道
-I've got my reasons for...  -I think I have a right to know.
好的 你想知道是么?
Okay. All right, you wanna know?
大约一年前...
About a year ago...
有人在向我们开枪?
Is someone shooting at us?
你肯定是法国女人
You must be the french chick.
-你是谁?  -Hurley
-Who are you?  -Hurley.
我
I
Sayid 那个你拷打过的人...他
Sayid...that guy you tortured...he
你那时在飞机上
You were on the plane.
听着 我来这是为了找...放松 别紧张 别紧张
Look, I came here to find...easy, easy. Easy.
我...我只是拿了你的笔记
I'm...I'm just getting your notes.
请...
Please...
你告诉我为什么你写下这些
tell me why you wrote this.
请告诉我这些数字代表了什么?
What do these numbers mean, please?
我不知道
I don't know.
什么?
What?
你不知道?
You don't know?
好的
Okay,
那个在丛林里的东西
that thing in the woods,
也许是只妖怪
maybe it's a monster,
也许是一只该死的长颈鹿 我不知道
maybe it's a pissed-off giraffe, I don't know.
那个没人在找我们的事实..
The fact that no one is even looking for us
是的 那很诡异
yeah, that's weird.
但是我只是去附和它
But I just go along with it
因为我赶了一程过来..
'cause I'm along for the ride...
只是为了好玩 老顽童Hurley
good old fun-time Hurley.
你想什么..
Well, guess what...
现在 我要一些怪异的回答
now, I want some freakin' answers!
我们的船截获了一串电波...
Our ship picked up a transmission...
一个重复着这些数字的声音
a voice repeating those numbers.
我们改变了计划去研究它
We changed course to investigate.
在我们的船只失事后
After we shipwrecked,
我的队伍继续搜寻着电波的来源
my team continued to search for the transmission source.
几周后在我们找到了电波发射塔
It was weeks before we found the radio tower.
岛上有电波发射塔?
There's a radio tower on this island?
在黑岩石上
Up by the black rock.
我们中的一些人继续着
Some of us continued
在等待救援的同时
to search for the meaning of those numbers
探索着这些号码的意义
while we waited for rescue.
但是那时 病魔袭来了
But then the sickness came.
当我的队伍都死了
When my team was gone,
我回到了那座塔 改变了电波
I went back up to the tower and changed the transmission.
就是我们听到的求救信号?
That distress signal we heard.
是的
Yes.
但是这些数字...
But the numbers...
你找到了有关它们的什么了么?
did you ever find out anything about them?
你知道它们怎么会有灵力的么?
Do you know where they got their power?
灵力?
Power?
它们给你周围的人带来厄运
They bring bad stuff to everyone around you.
它们是被诅咒的
They're cursed.
你是知道的 对么?
You know that, right?
这些号码...
The numbers...
它们被诅咒了
they're cursed.
我就是被这些号码带来这里的
The numbers are what brought me here.
在它出现之后
As it appears,
它们又带来了你
they brought you.
那之后
Since that time,
我失去了一切...
I've lost everything
每个我所关心的人
everyone I cared about.
那么 是的
So, yes,
我认为你是对的
I suppose you're right.
它们是被诅咒了的
They are cursed.
谢谢
Thank you.
你不会知道我为了有人赞同我
You have no idea how long I've been waiting
而等了多久
for someone to agree with me.
谢谢
Thank you.
上帝 谢谢你
god, thank you.
真的太谢谢你了
Thank you so much.
我们得找到Hurley和Charlie
We need to find Hurley and Charlie
然后走出这片丛林
and get out of this jungle.
我只是不想两手空空得回去
I just hate that we're going home empty-handed.
有人朝我们开枪...
someone shot at us...
Hurley和我
Hurley and me.
我们正在找你 然后...
We were looking for you, and...
-Hurley在哪儿?  -我不知道
-Where's Hurley?  -I don't know.
他本来就在我后面  然后他就...
He was right behind me, then he just...
他就不在了
he just wasn't.
-我去找他  -不 不 不 我们一起去
-I'll go and find him.  -No, no, no, we'll all go.
去哪儿?
Go where?
Hurley 该死的发生了什么事?
Hurley, what the hell happened to you?
要电池么?
Need a battery?
她说嘿
She says hey.
你想过名字了么?
You think of a name yet?
小孩的名字
For the baby.
我还没有好好想过
I haven't really thought about it.
我想放弃它
I was gonna give it away.
你知道 带给别人领养
You know, for adoption.
那肯定是一个艰苦的决定
That must have been a difficult decision.
现在没事了
Well, doesn't matter now.
今天是我的生日
It's my birthday today.
你为什么不跟任何人说?
Well, why haven't you told anyone?
我是一个怀孕的单身女人
I'm pregnant, single,
并且在一个荒野的岛上
and on an island in the middle of nowhere.
是不是我的生日真的是不重要 是么?
It doesn't really matter that it's my birthday, does it?
我想是的
I guess not.
至少你们的生日离得很近...
At least your birthdays will be close togethe...
你和你的孩子...那真是好运气
you and your baby --and that's good luck.
是么? 你这么认为?
Yeah? You think?
是的
Yeah, I do.
你相信...
You believe in that...
运气?
luck?
我相信很多事情
I believe in a lot of things.
做好了
That should do it.
好了 我放弃
Okay, I give up.
那是什么?
What is it?
一只摇篮
It's a cradle.
生日快乐 Claire
Happy birthday, Claire.
谢谢
Thank you.
我知道食物紧缺 但是你的衬衫?
I know food's scarce, but your shirt?
当你找到一个自助洗衣店 告诉我
When you find a laundromat, let me know.
回到丛林的时候
Back in the jungle,
在我们成为练习射击的靶子之前
before we became target practice,
你正要告诉我
you were gonna tell me
是什么驱使你去寻求的
what inspired this little quest.
我认为飞机失事可能是我的错
I think the plane crash might have been my fault.
别蠢了 你怎么可能...
Don't be daft. How could you possibly...
我们来这儿之前
before we came here,
很多坏事都发生了  而每次我都正好在周围
a lot of bad stuff used to happen whenever I was around.
你想说什么 像是厄运?
What do you mean, like bad luck?
是的 那是...
Yeah, that's...
那是一个描述那一切的恰当的词
that'd be kind of a mellow way of describing it.
坏事发生了
bad things happen.
飞机坠毁了 人死了
Planes crash, people die.
伙计 你真的应该让我先说完
Dude, you really oughta let me finish.
你认为你是唯一带行李的人么?
You think you're the only person with baggage?
你知道飞机往下掉的时候我在做什么么?
You know what I was doing when the plane went down?
我在吸海洛因
I was snorting heroin
在厕所
in the toilet.
我是一个有很大毒瘾的人
I was such a junkie,
甚至在坐飞机的时候都得去吸食
I couldn't even take a plane ride without having a fix.
我认为那也是你的错
I suppose that was your fault as well.
那么这怎么说?
So how 'bout it?
我刚刚告诉你了我这生最大的秘密
I just told you the biggest secret in my life.
我认为你应该说出你的来报答
I thought you'd wanna reciprocate
在家的时候...
Back home...
我有财产1亿5千6百万美元
I'm worth $156 million.
好了 别和我说了
Fine, don't tell me.
伙计
Dude.
我把灵魂都赤裸裸呈现出来了 然后我得到的是无聊的笑话
I bare my soul, and all I get is bloody jokes.
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报 ====